[
  {
    "question": "Question 1",
    "answer1": "Answer 1-1",
    "answer2": "Answer 1-2",
    "answer3": "Answer 1-3",
    "answer4": "Answer 1-4",
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "alreadyUsed": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 2",
    "answer1": "Answer 2-1",
    "answer2": "Answer 2-2",
    "answer3": "Answer 2-3",
    "answer4": "Answer 2-4",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "alreadyUsed": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 3",
    "answer1": "Answer 3-1",
    "answer2": "Answer 3-2",
    "answer3": "Answer 3-3",
    "answer4": "Answer 3-4",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "alreadyUsed": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 4",
    "answer1": "Answer 4-1",
    "answer2": "Answer 4-2",
    "answer3": "Answer 4-3",
    "answer4": "Answer 4-4",
    "correctAnswer": 4,
    "alreadyUsed": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 5",
    "answer1": "Answer 5-1",
    "answer2": "Answer 5-2",
    "answer3": "Answer 5-3",
    "answer4": "Answer 5-4",
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "alreadyUsed": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 6",
    "answer1": "Answer 6-1",
    "answer2": "Answer 6-2",
    "answer3": "Answer 6-3",
    "answer4": "Answer 6-4",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "alreadyUsed": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 7",
    "answer1": "Answer 7-1",
    "answer2": "Answer 7-2",
    "answer3": "Answer 7-3",
    "answer4": "Answer 7-4",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "alreadyUsed": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 8",
    "answer1": "Answer 8-1",
    "answer2": "Answer 8-2",
    "answer3": "Answer 8-3",
    "answer4": "Answer 8-4",
    "correctAnswer": 4,
    "alreadyUsed": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 9",
    "answer1": "Answer 9-1",
    "answer2": "Answer 9-2",
    "answer3": "Answer 9-3",
    "answer4": "Answer 9-4",
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "alreadyUsed": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 10",
    "answer1": "Answer 10-1",
    "answer2": "Answer 10-2",
    "answer3": "Answer 10-3",
    "answer4": "Answer 10-4",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "alreadyUsed": false
  }
]